http://www.portlandbolt.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
HomeProductsHeaded BoltsHex BoltsHeavy Hex BoltsStructural BoltsSquare Head BoltsTimber BoltsHeaded Anchor BoltsHex Lag ScrewSquare Lag ScrewsCarriage BoltsTimber SpikesMachine BoltsWasher Head BoltsRound Head BoltsCountersunk BoltsStep BoltsCustom HeadingRodsAnchor RodsAll Thread RodsTie RodsDrift PinsSwedged RodsThreaded RebarBent Bolts90° Anchor BoltRound U-BoltsSquare U-BoltsClosed Eye BoltOpen Eye BoltRound HookSquare HookJ-BoltsCustom BentAnchor Bolts and Anchor Rods90° Anchor BoltHeaded Anchor BoltsAnchor RodsAll Thread RodsSwedged RodsNutsHex NutsHeavy Hex NutsSquare NutsHex Jam NutsHeavy Jam NutsLock NutsHex Coupling NutsSleeve NutsWashersStandard WashersF436 Hardened WashersLock WashersMalleable Iron WashersRound Plate WashersSquare Plate WashersOgee WashersBeveled WashersHardened Beveled WashersClipped Hardened WashersLoad Indicating Washers (DTI)Rosette WashersHillside WashersOtherBarrier PinsPlatesTurnbucklesClevisesAnchor SleevesShear PlatesDapping ToolsSplit RingsGrooving ToolsBoat SpikesTechnical InformationCalculators & ToolsBolt Weight CalculatorTie Rod CalculatorPlate Weight CalculatorBolt Torque CalculatorFAQs: Ask the ExpertNewest FAQsThe ExpertsFAQ CategoriesAsk a QuestionSpecificationsAASHTOASTMSAECSAFastener Identification MarkingsStrength Requirements by GradeNut Compatibility ChartThread Pitch ChartSteel Hardness ConversionLag Screw Pilot Hole DiametersAASHTO to ASTM ConversionsStructural Bolt Weight ChartNut Weight ChartBolt Torque ChartBolt GlossaryProject ResumePower & EnergyIndustrialMarineBridgesCovered BridgesLight RailGovernment & MilitaryAmusement ParksStadiumsInternationalMiscellaneousVideosAbout UsContact UsMeet the TeamHistoryManufacturing CapabilitiesHot-Dip GalvanizingHeadingThreadingCuttingPlate FabricationBendingMiscellaneous CapabilitiesShippingCertification & TestingSteelIndustries ServedMarine ConstructionSteel FabricationHighway ContractorsTimber ConstructionPower and EnergyPrecast ConcreteLight Pole and Traffic SignalPole Line HardwareLight RailMiningOEMEngineers and ArchitectsGovernment and MilitaryRecent Shipment DestinationsTestimonialsNewsletterCredit ApplicationPB in the NewsCareersSocial MediaLeave FeedbackFun ZoneVideos
Our 2020 NFL Survivor Pool is underway
Home» Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Portland Bolt & Manufacturing Company strives to protect your privacy and respects the personal information you provide. It is our goal to clearly communicate the ways we use data you supply. This policy explains how we collect, protect and use information gathered on this site.
How we use the information
Portland Bolt uses information you provide about yourself and your company through online forms to address questions, respond to feedback and fulfill requests for information about products and services. We may use e-mail addresses you provide through our opt-in forms or sales process for direct electronic mail communication and offering campaigns, which may be of interest to you. Information you provide may be incorporated on the site with your consent.
We may use non-personal information like IP address or pages visited, to improve the site’s design and layout. We may use this information to analyze site usage and traffic.
We also may actively obtain information about you by installing a marker on your computer commonly called a “cookie.” Cookies enable choices to be recognized by identification unique to your computer. Personal information is only maintained when provided. Your web browser may be specifically configured to reject cookies, and you should refer to your web browser to learn how it treats cookies.
Your personal information is not sold, leased, loaned or traded to third parties.
Commitment to Security
We use commercially accepted measures consistent with industry practice to safeguard against unauthorized access or disclosure of information, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure appropriate use of your personal information.
Update/Change Information
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us at info@portlandbolt.com, calling us at the telephone number below or writing to us at the address below. We also may be contacted through our feedback form.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt-out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our site periodically.
Portland Bolt & Manufacturing
3441 NW Guam Street
Portland, OR 97210
(503) 227-5488
info@portlandbolt.com
